townfairtire.com 2016-05-14

# Town Fair Tire - Privacy Policy

UPDATED AS OF: January 14, 2015

Welcome to the Town Fair Tire (“Company” or “We”) website located at www.townfairtire.com (the “Website”). We are committed to maintaining your confidence and trust as it relates to the privacy of your information. Please read below and learn how we collect, protect, share and use your information. By using our Website, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with the following privacy policy. Note that this policy does not apply to information collected when you utilize a third-party website or to information collected when you apply for a Town Fair Tire credit card (issued by Credit First National Association). Town Fair Tire does not collect any information relating to credit card applications on its Website.

1\. INFORMATION COLLECTED ON OUR WEBSITE.

When you interact with us through the Website, we may collect certain personal data and other information from you, as further described below.

Information You Provide To Us.

Collection and Use of Personal Information. We receive and may keep information voluntarily given to us when you decided to make a purchase, register for an appointment on the Website, take part in an online special promotion, or provide any other information or unique preferences to better serve you. We may collect personal information (information that can be used to identify you as an individual) such as your name, email, and telephone number. The types of personal information we collect may vary depending on your use of the features of the Website. 

Information Collected Automatically.

Collection and Use of Usage Information. Whenever you visit or interact with our Website, we may use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect non-personally identifiable information about how the Website is accessed and used, such as browser type, device type, operating system, application version, the page served, the time, your geo-location, the preceding page views, and your use of features or applications on the Website. This information helps us keep our Website fresh and interesting to our visitors and allows us to tailor content to users’ interests. 

Collection and Use of IP Addresses. We or our service providers automatically collect your IP address you use to access the Website. We may use this information to administer the Website, help diagnose problems with our servers, analyze trends about a user’s use of the Website, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

Collection and Use of Cookies. When you visit our Website we store certain information on your computers or mobile devices known as “cookies.” Cookies may also be used to associate you with social networking sites like Facebook and Twitter and, if you so choose, enable interaction between your activities on the Website and your activities on such social networking sites. We, or our service providers, may place cookies or similar files on your computers or mobile device for security purposes, to facilitate site navigation and to personalize your experience while visiting our Website. 

A cookie is a small text file that a website can place on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping or other administrative purposes. Our Website may use cookies to help to personalize your experience on the Website. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Although most web browsers accept cookies automatically, usually you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you would prefer not to accept cookies, most browsers will allow you to: (i) change your browser settings to notify you when you receive a cookie, which lets you choose whether or not to accept it; or (ii) set your browser to automatically reject any cookies. If you decide to disable or decline cookies, you may not be able to fully use the features of the Website.

Use of Google Analytics and Google Adwords. We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this Website for remarketing purposes. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. Town Fair Tire uses the information obtained through the use of Google Analytics only to improve this Website. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. 

This Website also uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Website. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this Website, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics and Google Adwords about your visits to this Website is restricted by this privacy policy, Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this Website by disabling cookies on your browser. You can also set preferences for how Google advertises to you, including the option to opt-out of internet-based advertising on Google, by accessing and using the [Google Ad Preferences page.](http://www.google.com/settings/ads?hl=en&sig=ACi0TChANxthiApdkgeBVLjmOBbSwETOTwFBt6t5_zywzxC3qgdVEEXlAyLOznbEBu1dwwfDd75azxdHKuK1Z-IUDlw1lIWvDQ)

2\. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED

We use the information we collect about and from you to answer your questions and requests; provide you with access to certain areas and features of the Website; verify your identity; communicate with you about your activities on the Website, e.g., scheduling an appointment; tailor content, advertisements, and offers we advertise to you for marketing purposes, such as generating remarketing; improve the Website; comply with license obligations; and for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your personal information or otherwise with your consent. We may also use the information we collect to administer giveaways, contests, and promotions.

3\. SHARING OF INFORMATION

We restrict access to non-public personal information submitted by you on the Website to those employees and other third parties who need to know the information in order for us to provide certain services to you. Town Fair Tire does not sell or rent the personal information you choose to provide to us to any third party. Also, we will not disclose the personal information you provide to us to any third party without your consent, except (a) as required by law; (b) to third party service providers that host, maintain, service or operate the Website, (c) to service providers where the disclosure will enable that party to perform business, professional or technical support, and (d) with our subsidiaries, affiliates, sponsors, partners, advertisers or other third parties to provide you with product information and promotional and other offers. 

4\. INFORMATION WE RECEIVE FROM THIRD PARTIES

We may receive information about you from third parties. For example, you may choose to participate in a third party application or feature, such as one our Facebook, Twitter, Google, LinkedIn or Blogger applications or a similar application or feature on a third party website, through which you allow us to collect (or the third party to share) information about you, including usage information and personal information. In addition, we may receive information about you if other users of a third party website give us access to their profiles and you are one of their "connections" or information about you is otherwise accessible through your "connections” web page, profile page, or similar page on a social networking or other third party website or interactive service.

5\. YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS, CHOICE AND ACCESS.

You may always direct us not to share your personal information with third parties, not to use your personal information to provide you with information or offers, or not to send you newsletters, emails or other communications by: (i) sending us an email at [custservice@townfair.com](mailto:custservice@townfair.com); or (ii) contacting us by mail at Town Fair Tire, 460 Coe Avenue, East Haven, CT 06512. Your opt-out request will be processed within 30 days of the date on which we receive it. Please note that we do not control certain privacy settings and preferences maintained by our social media partners like Facebook, Twitter, Google, LinkedIn or Blogger. If you wish to make changes to those settings and preferences, you may do so by visiting the settings page of the appropriate social media site.

6\. CHILDREN.

The Website is only intended for adults and is not directed to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personally identifiable information from anyone under 13 years of age. If we determine upon collection that a user is under this age, we will not use or maintain his/her personal information without parental/guardian consent. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, we will make reasonable efforts to delete such information from our records.

7\. CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY.

We may make changes to the information, content and/or policies contained on this Website or the offering and/or services described in this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices at any time. We reserve the right to make changes or add to this privacy policy at any time without notice, so we encourage you to review it periodically. Town Fair Tire makes no commitment and undertakes no obligation for it or its users to update the information contained herein.

8\. CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the general terms of use of the Website, or your dealing with this Website, you may contact us at:
